hey guys welcome to this probability
question you flip a coin
two times what is the probability you
get two heads the best way to do this is
to
show all the possible outcomes we're
gonna flip the coin twice so we have our
first toss and our second toss so our
first toss can be a head and our second
toss can be a head or our first toss
could be a head
and our second toss could be a tail our
first toss could be a tail and the
second could be a head
or the first toss could be a tail and
the second could be a tail this
should represent all possible outcomes
each of these has an equal probability
of happening
so there's a one and four chance so now
was it probably of getting two heads
well this
is the one scenario where we get two
heads so the answer is one
fourth as a percent that would be 25 and
that's the answer to the question if you
flip a coin twice the problem of you
getting two heads in a row
is 25 comment below on what you'd like
me to solve next and i'll talk to you
soon
bye